(Josh:)Amazing.
(Guy:)I know.
(Sheldon:)This isn't the printout.
(Sheldon:)This is my real face.
(Amy:)What are we doing?
(Amy:)This is a fort.
(Amy:)Let's sit on the floor.
(Sheldon:)Roughing it? Okay.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)Everything looks
so big from down here.
(Sheldon:)This must be
how Leonard feels.
(Howard:)I'm surprised
you could hear me
(Howard:)with this Thin Mint
in your ear!
(laughs)
(Howard:)Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Kevin:)Anyway,
I should probably get going.
(Bernadette:)Howie, have you
noticed how often
(Bernadette:)people say that
when you start to do magic?
(Josh:)Sorry, I have a long drive.
(Howard:)Well, I hope I get
to see you again.
(chuckles)
I hope so, too.